question_data = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]

more_questions = [{"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "The Cold War ended with Joseph Stalin&#039;s death.",
                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean",
                   "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                   "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                   "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                   "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
                   "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "In the &quot;Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&quot; series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                   "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                  {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "California is larger than Japan.",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                  {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "BMW M GmbH is a subsidiary of BMW AG that focuses on car performance.",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                  {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                   "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.",
                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                  {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean",
                   "difficulty": "easy",
                   "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
